yogaglo.com 2011-11-01

# We Respect Your Privacy - Yoga Glo Policy | YogaGlo.com

Last modified: June 15, 2008

At Yogaglo we recognize that privacy is important and we are committed to protecting your privacy rights ("Policy"). We use the information we collect about you to process orders, to improve the content of the Website and to provide a more personalized experience. We may also use it to periodically inform you about changes on our Website and new products and services. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Yogaglo, LLC (the "Website" or "Yogaglo"), any Yogaglo software that you have embedded on a website or are about to embed ("Yogaglo Widgets"), any applications created by Yogaglo and available through social networking sites ("Yogaglo Apps") or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, Yogaglo's "Service").

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:info@yogaglo.com).

By using the Service, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Policy. As this Policy may be amended from time to time, you should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Policy.

In addition to information about yourself, you may submit other content ("Content"). To protect your privacy, the Service allows you to mark your Content as "Private", in which event it can only be seen by you and people with whom the unique URL of your Content has been shared, or in accordance with the terms applicable to social networking sites on which you include Content through Yogaglo Apps. However, Yogaglo has no responsibility for how people you allow to view your Content (or the public if you make any information available to the public) use that material, or to whom they may forward it. Moreover, if you "embed" a Yogaglo Widget on another web page or share Content through an Yogaglo App, it will be visible to the public in accordance with the policies of that web page, regardless of whether you have restricted access to that Content on Yogaglo.

When you install an Yogaglo App on your social network page or use an Yogaglo App on someone else's page, we may record information regarding the use of that Yogaglo App, and we may collect other information that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with that page. When you invite new members into your network or send messages through the Yogaglo Service, we collect and maintain on secure servers the information associated with those messages, including email addresses and content.

Finally, in order to provide the best possible service and to allow us to make certain internal reports and make recommendations, we collect aggregate information about the use of the Service, including information about users accessing the Website or viewing Yogaglo Widgets or using Yogaglo Apps on other sites, such as internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time ("Activity Information").

By using the Service, you consent to our retaining all the above-described information in anonymous form indefinitely.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

**Information you provide** \- When you sign up for a Yogaglo account we ask you for personal information (such as your name, e-mail address and an account password and may require your date of birth, gender and zip code). After your 15 day free trial period, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Yogaglo services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.

We make your profile available to other users according to the privacy settings you set for yourself as part of your profile. Your user name will be identified to us and to any recipient of messages you send through the Service.

We also use your name, e-mail address and other information on our system to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. In the event that we decide to allow you to submit other information about yourself, the availability of that information to other users will also be controlled by privacy settings you will set for yourself. In the event that you make your Yogaglo Widgets publicly available, or "embed" them on another publicly available web site (such as a social networking site), we may include links to those shows or web sites or otherwise identify them in our marketing materials as places where Yogaglo Widgets that may interest other users can be found.

**Yogaglo cookies** \- When you visit Yogaglo, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Yogaglo features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**IP Address** \- An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. We may retain your IP address in order to help us diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our Website, to help identify you, to gather broad anonymous demographic information (such as the number of visitors from a geographic area), to enforce compliance with the Website terms and conditions or otherwise in order to protect our services, sites, customers, or others.

**Log information** \- When you use the Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

**User communications** \- When you send email or other communication to Yogaglo, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**Affiliated sites** \- We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. Personal information that you provide to those websites may be sent to Yogaglo in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated websites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

**Links** \- Yogaglo may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our Website.

**Other websites** \- This Policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by Yogaglo. We do not exercise control over the websites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

Yogaglo only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and
  * Developing new services.

Yogaglo processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

**Choices For Personal Information**

When you sign up for the Service, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Yogaglo may not be able to provide those services to you.

**Information Sharing**

Yogaglo only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Yogaglo in the following limited circumstances:

We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Yogaglo, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Yogaglo becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such information does not identify you individually.

**Information Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Yogaglo employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Data Integrity**

Yogaglo processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Accessing and Updating Personal Information**

When you use Yogaglo services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

**Enforcement**

Yogaglo regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Yogaglo's treatment of personal information by [contacting us](mailto:info@yogaglo.com).

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Yogaglo's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Yogaglo and an individual.

**Children Under 13**

Yogaglo content is not directed at children under 13 years of age, and if you provide information about yourself as a user of Yogaglo, you are representing that you are 13 years of age or older. If you are younger than 13 years of age and would like to become a registered member of or provide information about yourself to the Website, you are required to have your parent or legal guardian contact Yogaglo at [info@yogaglo.com](mailto:info@yogaglo.com) prior to use.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age, but if we do become aware of having collected personally identifiable information from a user who is younger than 13 years of age without prior, verifiable consent from a parent or legal guardian, we will remove such information from our files.

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

**Changes To This Policy**

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

**Third Party Links, Co-brand Relationships and Public Forums**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, Yogaglo may choose various third party web sites to link to, link from, and frame within, the Website. Yogaglo also may participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to its users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with Yogaglo, we have no control over these linked sites, each of who have separate privacy and data collection practices independent of Yogaglo. We have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. Please make sure you are comfortable with the privacy practices of every site you visit before providing the site with your personal information. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk.

We also may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to you on the Website. Please remember that we cannot control the information that is shared by members and that anything you voluntarily provide in any public area of the Internet will be publicly available to other visitors on that web site and potentially to other third parties. Thus, please note that you should always exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose any of your personal information in these and similar areas.

**Yogaglo Terms and Conditions of Use**

A complete statement of our Terms and Conditions of Use can be found here. Yogaglo's Terms and Conditions of Use are expressly incorporated into this Policy by this reference.

**Your consent**

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Yogaglo as set forth in this Policy. If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what limited circumstances we disclose it. Continued access or use of the Website shall constitute your express acceptance of any modifications to this Policy.
